<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="72">
    <author>Az#4971</author>
    <version>1.2.1.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Upgradable Factories</en>
        <fr>Usines Améliorables</fr>
        <de>Aufrüstbare Fabriken</de>
        <ru>Улучшаемые Производства</ru>
        <br>Fábricas atualizáveis</br>
        <it>Fabbriche potenziabili</it>
	    <tr>Yükseltilebilir Fabrikalar</tr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Upgrade your production facilities! With this mod you will be able to increase your production speeds and storages, so you no longer need to place multiple productions.
Features :
- Production chains now have levels that you can increase.
- Upgrading a factory will cost you slightly more each level than buying a new building.
- Upgrading cost is vastly compensated by the gain in production speed.
- More production speed means more storage space.
- Because you don't have to build a new facility, you save on production costs.
- Factory value is increased when upgrading, so you can claim your investment back when selling a facility.

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.1.0">1.2.1.0</a>
- Added Turkish translation

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.0.0">1.2.0.0</a>
- Added BR and IT translations
- Fixed a bug blocking the game loading at 99%
- Fixed a bug where levels were not properly attributed after restart
- Pumps n' Hoses compatibility. The PnH biogas system being modular you will not be able to upgrade it with this mod
- Fixed an issue when deleting the mod where the production values where not reset

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.1.0.0">1.1.0.0</a>
- Added RU translation
- Fixed a bug blocking the game loading at 99%
- Factories now have a maximum level (default 10)
- Added a console command to modify factory max level (ufMaxLevel)

Note that the maximum level you can reach is 10.
As of yet, this mod does not support multiplayer.
More info on <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories">GitHub</a>.
Thanks to the github contributors]]>
        </en>
        <fr><![CDATA[
Améliorez vos installations de production ! Avec ce mod, vous pourrez augmenter vos vitesses de production et de stockages, de sorte que vous n'aurez plus besoin de placer plusieurs productions.
Caractéristiques :
- Les chaînes de production ont maintenant des niveaux que vous pouvez augmenter.
- L'amélioration d'une usine vous coûtera légèrement plus cher à chaque niveau que l'achat d'un nouveau bâtiment.
- Le coût d'amélioration est largement compensé par le gain en vitesse de production.
- Plus de vitesse de production signifie plus d'espace de stockage.
- Comme vous n'avez pas besoin de construire une nouvelle usine, vous économisez sur les coûts de production.
- La valeur de l'usine augmente lors de la mise à niveau, ce qui vous permet de récupérer votre investissement lors de la vente d'une installation.

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.1.0">1.2.1.0</a>
- Ajout de la traduction turc

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.0.0">1.2.0.0</a>
- Ajout des traductions brésilienne et italienne
- Correction d'un bug bloquant le chargement à 99%
- Correction d'un bug où les niveaux n'étaient pas correctement attribués après le redémarrage.
- Compatibilité avec Pumps n' Hoses. Le système de biogaz PnH étant modulaire, vous ne pourrez pas le mettre à jour avec ce mod.
- Correction d'un problème lors de la suppression du mod où la valeur des productions n'était pas réinitialisée.

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.1.0.0">1.1.0.0</a>
- Ajout de la traduction russe
- Correction d'un bug bloquant le chargement à 99%
- Les usines ont maintenant un niveau maximum (par défaut 10)
- Ajout d'une commande pour modifier le niveau maximum des usines (ufMaxLevel)

Notez que le niveau maximal que vous pouvez atteindre est 10.
Ce mod ne supporte pas encore le multijoueur.
Plus d'informations sur <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories">GitHub</a>.
Merci aux contributeurs de github]]>
        </fr>
        <de><![CDATA[
Verbessern Sie Ihre Produktionsanlagen! Mit dieser Mod können Sie Ihre Produktionsgeschwindigkeiten und Lagerräume erhöhen, so dass Sie nicht mehr mehrere Produktionen platzieren müssen.
Eigenschaften:
- Produktionsketten haben jetzt Stufen, die Sie erhöhen können.
- Das Aufrüsten einer Fabrik kostet dich etwas mehr pro Stufe als der Kauf eines neuen Gebäudes.
- Die Kosten für die Aufrüstung werden durch den Gewinn an Produktionsgeschwindigkeit bei weitem kompensiert.
- Mehr Produktionsgeschwindigkeit bedeutet mehr Lagerplatz.
- Da Sie keine neue Anlage bauen müssen, sparen Sie Produktionskosten.
- Der Wert der Fabrik wird durch die Aufrüstung erhöht, so dass Sie beim Verkauf einer Anlage Ihre Investition zurückerhalten können.

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.1.0">1.2.1.0</a>
- Türkische Übersetzung hinzugefügt

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.0.0">1.2.0.0</a>
- Brasilianische und italienische Übersetzungen hinzugefügt
- Ein Fehler wurde behoben, der das Laden des Spiels bei 99% blockierte.
- Ein Fehler wurde behoben, bei dem Ebenen nach einem Neustart nicht korrekt zugeordnet wurden.
- Kompatibilität mit Pumps n' Hoses. Da das PnH-Biogassystem modular aufgebaut ist, können Sie es mit diesem Mod nicht aufrüsten.
- Ein Problem beim Löschen des Mods wurde behoben, bei dem der Wert der Produktionen nicht zurückgesetzt wurde.

Changelog <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.1.0.0">1.1.0.0</a>
- Russische Übersetzung hinzugefügt
- Ein Fehler wurde behoben, der das Laden des Spiels bei 99% blockierte.
- Fabriken haben jetzt eine maximale Stufe (Standard 10)
- Konsolenbefehl zum Ändern des maximalen Levels von Fabriken hinzugefügt (ufMaxLevel)

Dass die maximale Stufe, die Sie erreichen können, 10 ist.
Diese Mod unterstützt noch keinen Multiplayer.
Mehr Infos auf <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories">GitHub</a>.
Dank an die Github-Mitarbeiter]]>
        </de>
        <it><![CDATA[
Aggiorna i tuoi impianti di produzione! Con questa mod sarai in grado di aumentare le tue velocità di produzione ed i tuoi depositi, quindi non avrai più bisogno di posizionare più produzioni.
Caratteristiche :
- Le catene di produzione ora hanno livelli che puoi aumentare.
- L'aggiornamento di una fabbrica ti costerà leggermente di più per ogni livello rispetto all'acquisto di un nuovo edificio.
- Il costo di aggiornamento è ampiamente compensato dall'aumento della velocità di produzione.
- Più velocità di produzione significa più spazio di archiviazione.
- Poiché non devi costruire una nuova struttura, risparmi sui costi di produzione.
- Il valore della fabbrica aumenta durante l'aggiornamento, quindi puoi richiedere il rimborso dell'investimento quando vendi una struttura.

Registro delle modifiche <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.1.0">1.2.1.0</a>
- Aggiunta la traduzione in turco

Registro delle modifiche <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.2.0.0">1.2.0.0</a>
- Aggiunta di traduzioni BR e IT
- Risolto un bug che bloccava il caricamento del gioco al 99%
- Risolto un bug per cui i livelli non venivano attribuiti correttamente dopo il riavvio
- Compatibilità con Pumps n' Hoses. Essendo il sistema di biogas PnH modulare, non sarà possibile aggiornarlo con questa modifica.
- Corretto un problema durante l'eliminazione della mod in cui il valore delle produzioni non veniva ripristinato.

Registro delle modifiche <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories/releases/tag/v1.1.0.0">1.1.0.0</a>
- Aggiunta la traduzione RU
- Risolto un bug che bloccava il caricamento del gioco al 99%
- Le fabbriche ora hanno un livello massimo (predefinito 10)
- Aggiunto un comando da console per modificare il livello massimo di fabbrica (ufMaxLevel)

Nota che il livello massimo che puoi raggiungere è 10.
Al momento, questa mod non supporta il multiplayer.
Ulteriori informazioni su <a href="https://github.com/Percedal/FS22_UpgradableFactories">GitHub</a>.
Grazie ai collaboratori di github]]>
       </it>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="false"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="UpgradableFactories.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <l10n>
        <text name="uf_upgrade">
            <en>Upgrade</en>
            <fr>Améliorer</fr>
            <de>Upgrade</de>
            <ru>Улучшить</ru>
            <br>Atualização</br>
            <it>Aggiornamento</it>
		    <tr>Yükselt</tr>
        </text>
        <text name="uf_upgrade_dialog">
            <en>Upgrade %s to level %d for %s?</en>
            <fr>Améliorer %s au niveau %d pour %s ?</fr>
            <de>Upgrade %s auf Stufe %d. Kosten: %s?</de>
            <ru>Улучшить %s до уровня %d за %s?</ru>
            <br>Atualização %s para o nível %d para %s?</br>
            <it>Aggiorna %s al livello %d per %s?</it>
		    <tr>%s %d seviyeye %s karşılığında yükseltilsin mi?</tr>
        </text>
        <text name="uf_max_level">
            <en>Your production is already at maximum level.</en>
            <fr>Votre production est déjà au niveau maximum.</fr>
            <de>Ihre Produktion ist bereits auf dem Höchststand.</de>
            <ru>Ваше производство уже на максимальном уровне.</ru>
            <br>Sua produção já está no nível máximo.</br>
            <it>La tua produzione è già al massimo livello.</it>
		    <tr>Üretiminiz zaten maksimum seviyede.</tr>
        </text>
    </l10n>
</modDesc>
